<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>生活小知識 on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/%E7%94%9F%E6%B4%BB%E5%B0%8F%E7%9F%A5%E8%AD%98/</link><description>Recent content in 生活小知識 on SteveYi's Blog</description><image><url>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</url><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 10:00:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/%E7%94%9F%E6%B4%BB%E5%B0%8F%E7%9F%A5%E8%AD%98/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Method to add real-time lyrics to Spotify or other music software (Android)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/dynamic-lyrics-android/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 10:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/dynamic-lyrics-android/</guid><description>Last time, we introduced the comparison of free memberships among various streaming platforms. As you can see, many platforms have real-time lyrics. However, according to our testing, only Spotify Premium users can use them, and some platforms do not offer lyric services, which is a bit of a shame.
Do you find it inconvenient to listen to free music on Spotify or other platforms without lyrics? If so, follow this article to solve this problem.</description></item><item><title>No subscription required for Youtube Music Premium to enable background playback on iOS/iPadOS (also works for Youtube!)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-ios/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 14:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-ios/</guid><description>Here we mainly use iPad as an example, but the same method can be applied to iPhone as well. Android devices can also use a similar method, and a tutorial for Android will be posted in the future, so stay tuned for more articles from &amp;ldquo;I am Little Yi&amp;rdquo;!
Update: Android tutorial is available here
Recently, the author has been looking for a good free streaming music service, and found that the Youtube Music App on the computer (actually embedded in the webpage) is quite user-friendly.</description></item></channel></rss>