<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/</link><description>Recent content on SteveYi's Blog</description><image><url>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</url><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 01:07:22 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Import and Apply Excel Data in Indesign Templates</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/indesign-import-excel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 01:07:22 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/indesign-import-excel/</guid><description>Recently, the SITCON Hour of Code programming event has ended! We are also preparing thank-you notes for the teaching assistants.
This time, we asked 小妘 to help design the template, so I want to record how to import Excel data and apply the template in Indesign.
Prepare Excel document First, we organize the data in the Excel document and put the &amp;ldquo;data name&amp;rdquo; in the first row.
The data name here will replace the text in Indesign, so it is strongly recommended to use English.</description></item><item><title>PVE Configuration of Arista LACP Link Aggregation</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/configuring-lacp-link-aggregation-in-pve-with-arista/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 02:39:05 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/configuring-lacp-link-aggregation-in-pve-with-arista/</guid><description>Recently, we encountered a machine using two NVIDIA Mellanox ConnectX-4 network cards, with maximum speed support of 25G. However, since our optical module is only 10G, and Arista 7050QX also cannot support 25G Only, we decided to set up LACP.
Environment Arista 7050QX-32S Proxmox VE ovs-vsctl (Open vSwitch) 2.15.0 LACP Configuration on Arista This is divided into two steps:
Establish a Port Channel Assign Port Channel to physical network cards Note: Keep the switchport part as is, and remember to set up both Port Channel and Ethernet Interface on both ends.</description></item><item><title>Cisco N3K-C3048TP-1GE Upgrade from 6.x to 9.x Full Process</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/upgrade-c3048tp-from-6.x-to-9.x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 01:51:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/upgrade-c3048tp-from-6.x-to-9.x/</guid><description>Recently, I had a N3K-C3048TP-1GE switch with an outdated version causing some issues, so I decided to upgrade to a new version to solve these problems!
Major version upgrades have certain risks, so please read this article and the official document before deciding whether to proceed!
Environment Before Upgrading Model: N3K-C3048TP-1GE-SUP
NXOS: 6.0(2)U3(4)
Important reminder:
Please follow the guide to upgrade this switch and do not upgrade to the latest version at once!</description></item><item><title>How to Upgrade Your iOS Device to Beta Version</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/how-to-upgrade-ios-rc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 19:00:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/how-to-upgrade-ios-rc/</guid><description>Recently, iOS 16.3 RC was released, and as usual, the release of the RC version means that the official version update will be released in a week as well, and the two versions are no different.
So, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at how to upgrade your iOS device to RC/Beta version.
How to Get Testing Qualifications There are basically two ways to download the iOS Beta version testing qualifications:
Apple Beta Software Program Apple Developer Program Apple Beta Software Program Apple Beta Software Program is a public testing program provided by Apple.</description></item><item><title>Configuring OOB Network on Arista</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/arista-mgmt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 02:58:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/arista-mgmt/</guid><description>Recently deployed an Arista switch. As L3 Routing was configured on this switch, it was not possible to set the OOB network as the default route...</description></item><item><title>Encountering Dynamic Linking Library Missing Issue when Building Golang</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/dynamic-link-library-missing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 15:36:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/dynamic-link-library-missing/</guid><description>During Golang build, encountering dynamic linking library missing issue...</description></item><item><title>Make a RESTFul API to upload files to S3 with Golang</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-golnag-to-upload-file-to-s3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 04:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-golnag-to-upload-file-to-s3/</guid><description>Anyway, I need have a API to upload files to S3 (Eg: image, iso file ...etc)</description></item><item><title>A capitalizations name issue can not build golang app</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/capitalizations-name-issue-in-golang/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 17:40:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/capitalizations-name-issue-in-golang/</guid><description>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;m working on a project which is a URL Shortener with Golang.
Here is current architecture.
steveyiyo@SteveYis-MacBook-Pro-2 URL-Shortener % tree . ├── README.md ├── config.yaml ├── config.yaml.example ├── data.db ├── details.md ├── dockerfile ├── go.mod ├── go.sum ├── internal │ ├── cache │ │ ├── cache.go │ │ └── cache_test.go │ ├── Database │ │ └── database.go │ └── Tools │ └── tools.go ├── main.go └── package └── utils └── utils.</description></item><item><title>Acquires AS7480 (Inter-RIR transfer)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/as7480/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/as7480/</guid><description>History IANA earlier assigned AS7467 - 7722 to APNIC and APNIC assigned it to their members or other legal entities.
% IANA WHOIS server % for more information on IANA, visit http://www.iana.org % This query returned 1 object refer: whois.apnic.net as-block: 7467-7722 organisation: Assigned by APNIC whois: whois.apnic.net descr: Assigned by APNIC source: IANA Recently, Jason decided to change their network service provider. It&amp;rsquo;s mean they didn&amp;rsquo;t need multihoming, so he decided to transfer AS Number to me.</description></item><item><title>Implementing Virtual WAN Multi-PPPoe on Linux</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/multi-pppoe-in-linux/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 08:47:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/multi-pppoe-in-linux/</guid><description>I&amp;#39;ve been using Linux as a router for quite some time.</description></item><item><title>Open VRF Module in Linux</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/enable-vrf-linux-krenel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 02:26:41 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/enable-vrf-linux-krenel/</guid><description>Recently, I installed a new router and found that the VRF module did not load successfully because I was using the image provided by the service provider.
root@eu-router:/opt/tunnel# modprobe vrf modprobe: FATAL: Module vrf not found in directory /lib/modules/5.4.0-72-generic My Linux Kernel is 5.4.0-72-generic, so I installed the extension package.
apt install linux-modules-extra-`uname -r` Then, load the VRF module again. If there is no response, it means that it was successful!</description></item><item><title>Using AS-SET to build filters</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-as-set-to-make-filter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 05:35:35 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-as-set-to-make-filter/</guid><description>Recently, in order to establish BGP Peers with some friends who are new to the field, I also taught them how to use AS-SET for filtering.
What is AS-SET AS-SET is an object that can add ASN and AS-SET.
Usually used to filter routes exchanged through the BGP protocol. (such as BGP Peer Neighbor, Internet Exchange Route Server, etc.)
We usually query all Route Objects in this AS-SET through Whois and recursion.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Policy Based Routing with FRRouting</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/frrouting-pbr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 16:23:58 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/frrouting-pbr/</guid><description>A few days ago, I was adjusting the network architecture in my lab to allow everything to go out through VPN and access my intranet. This led me to research Policy Based Routing (PBR).
I initially used VRF (Layer 3 switching) to isolate my network, but this prevented me from running my services on the VRF interface. This meant that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t set up DoH on the router.
Later, I discovered that I could use other methods to achieve PBR without using VRF.</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Intranet with OSPF and BGP</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ospf-and-bgp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 22:17:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ospf-and-bgp/</guid><description>For a long time, my friends and I have had an intranet similar to DN42. We use VPN to establish BGP connections and deploy this intranet using various devices in different areas.
P.S. Currently, there are about 46 routes.
Currently, I am building a BGP peer with other people from one point and using static routes to handle internal routing.
For example, if the device 10.121.23.242 wants to reach a device 10.</description></item><item><title>Solving the 53 Port Occupancy Issue on Ubuntu</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ubuntu-53-port-already-in-use/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 20:58:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ubuntu-53-port-already-in-use/</guid><description>Recently, in order to install a DoH Client on my router and set up a DNS server for internal network devices, I found that Ubuntu often uses port 53.
After checking, I found that this was caused by systemd-resolve, so I found these methods to disable it!
Before that, if you find that port 53 is being used, you can use the following command to see which process is using it.</description></item><item><title>Set .tmpl files as HTML syntax in VSCode</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/set_tmpl_file_as_html_in_vscode/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 09:57:13 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/set_tmpl_file_as_html_in_vscode/</guid><description>When I started learning Golang recently, I used .tmpl as a web template. However, I found that it couldn&amp;rsquo;t handle formatting automatically like HTML files. P.S. Even with related plugins installed, it only processes .html files.
After checking some related documents, I found that I can modify user settings to handle it. Here are two methods:
The first method is to directly modify the settings.json file and add the following code at the bottom:</description></item><item><title>Hosting a Minecraft Server on Linux</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/hosting-a-minecraft-server-on-linux/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 17:56:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/hosting-a-minecraft-server-on-linux/</guid><description>Recently, a friend of mine wanted to set up a Minecraft server on Linux, so I decided to write down the process here!
Environment In this setup, I used the following operating system and packages:
Ubuntu 20.04 Server byobu openjdk-8-jdk spigot 1.16.5 Update System and Install Packages To update the system, we enter the following command:
apt update -y apt upgrade -y Next, install Java and Byobu:
apt install openjdk-8-jdk byobu -y Deploy Minecraft Server First, we create a folder to place the server files:</description></item><item><title>Installing DHCP Server on Linux</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/install-dhcp-server-on-linux/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 09:37:30 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/install-dhcp-server-on-linux/</guid><description>I often use Linux systems as routers for the simple reason that virtual machines require them. But I thought, since I&amp;rsquo;m doing it anyway, why not write a blog post about it?
So&amp;hellip; let&amp;rsquo;s get started with the installation!
Installing isc-dhcp-server First, we need to install a package called isc-dhcp-server.
sudo apt install isc-dhcp-server Configuring DHCP Server After installation, we need to edit the configuration file /etc/dhcp/dhcpd.conf. Here&amp;rsquo;s an example:</description></item><item><title>Pin Any Tweet on Your Twitter Profile</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/pin-any-tweet-on-twitter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 19:00:27 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/pin-any-tweet-on-twitter/</guid><description>Today, while browsing Twitter, I came across an interesting tweet&amp;hellip;
So I immediately shared it with @edisonlee55
It&amp;rsquo;s obvious that this person has retweeted someone else&amp;rsquo;s tweet and pinned it to their own profile page.
This seems normal, but in fact, &amp;ldquo;we can only pin tweets that we ourselves have posted.&amp;rdquo; When we click on a tweet that we retweeted, we don&amp;rsquo;t see the &amp;ldquo;pin tweet&amp;rdquo; option.
So&amp;hellip; we need a little trick!</description></item><item><title>Setting up NAT on iptables</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/iptables_nat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 13:20:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/iptables_nat/</guid><description>Recently, Xiaoyi installed Ubuntu 20.04 on a computer at home and used it as a soft router.
But Xiaoyi found that the computer couldn&amp;rsquo;t connect to the internet!
After using mtr to trace the route, we found that the route could not go beyond the Gateway. So we captured packets on the router and found that our internal IP was sent to the ISP, but there was no response.
If the ISP hasn&amp;rsquo;t configured it properly, it can easily lead to IP Spoofing.</description></item><item><title>Using checkm8 Activation Lock Free Version to Bypass iOS Activation Lock</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/checkm8-bypass/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:35:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/checkm8-bypass/</guid><description>This article is also published on &amp;ldquo;蘿蔔&amp;rsquo;s Blog&amp;rdquo;
[Note] Please do not use for commercial or illegal purposes.
This software was not developed by the author. The author is not responsible for any controversies arising from its use. To bypass activation lock, you need a Mac computer.
The author tested the software on their own device with their own account (iPhone 7 Plus, iOS 14.3). Sometimes, due to certain reasons, when an iPhone is reset or updated without turning off &amp;ldquo;Find My&amp;rdquo;, you will be asked for the Apple ID password to disable activation lock when resetting it.</description></item><item><title>Migrating from WordPress to Hugo</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/from-wordpress-to-hugo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 14:27:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/from-wordpress-to-hugo/</guid><description>After registering my first domain, steveyigame.com, in 2018, I tried to set up my first WordPress blog. At that time, I was also learning to use Linux systems and came to understand the difference between cloud drives (like Google Drive) and file servers.
Why Switch to Hugo? Is WordPress Not Good? I believe there is no such thing as good or bad, it&amp;rsquo;s all personal preference. However, as I gradually learned about backend development, I thought, &amp;ldquo;If it can be a static website, let it be static and don&amp;rsquo;t let the website server handle things.</description></item><item><title>Designating network egress by AS Number</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/bgp-asn-specify-gateway/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 02:13:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/bgp-asn-specify-gateway/</guid><description>In January of last year, I applied for my first ASN - AS209557, and did a lot of cool experiments!
Today, I reconfigured my home router and can now designate which route to take based on ASN.
First, let me introduce my router information Ubuntu 20.04 software router
Bird2 (Internet Routing Daemon)
Network environment (including VPN tunnel) Chunghwa Telecom PPPoe non-fixed IP 100/40M
To TANet&amp;rsquo;s WireGuard Tunnel
To GCP&amp;rsquo;s WireGuard Tunnel</description></item><item><title>Become a MANRS participant!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/join-manrs-as-participants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:03:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/join-manrs-as-participants/</guid><description>At the end of last year, I submitted an application for MANRS for SteveYi Network Service. At the beginning of this year, we passed the review and officially became a participant in MANRS! Our member introduction can be found here: https://www.manrs.org/isps/participants/entry/1484/
So, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about how we implement MANRS policies.
MANRS has four main policies, which are:
Prevent propagation of incorrect routing information Prevent traffic with incorrect spoofed source IP addresses Promote coordination between network operators Facilitate global operational communication and coordination</description></item><item><title>Building an Internal Network with Friends using BGP</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/make-internal-network-by-bgp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/make-internal-network-by-bgp/</guid><description>Hi! Long time no see!
In early 2020, I obtained my first ASN number - AS209557
I also used IP Addresses defined by RFC 1918, and with some friends, I built a large internal network using BGP and Internet tunnels.
So let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
First, we use Ubuntu 20.04 to establish a tunnel and establish BGP peerings with others.
Usually, I use GRE, SIT, or WireGuard.
Among them, GRE or SIT tunnels are non-encrypted tunnels that can be viewed on the public network.</description></item><item><title>Google Ads - This is How Google Sees You...</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/google-adssettings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/google-adssettings/</guid><description>This article was supposed to be published in December of last year, but it happened to coincide with server maintenance, so it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been released until now.
One day, when the author was modifying their Google account information, they accidentally discovered the &amp;ldquo;Ad Settings&amp;rdquo; section, which had quite a bit of information.
The data comes from various records of Google and YouTube under the login status, as well as the basic information filled out when applying for a Google account.</description></item><item><title>Easy integration with Google Drive in Linux environment</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/linux-mount-googledrive-not-required-brain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 12:25:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/linux-mount-googledrive-not-required-brain/</guid><description>This tutorial uses the software google-drive-ocamlfuse and the demonstration is based on the Ubuntu-based Zorin OS 15.2 system.
First, you need to add the software source. Please enter the following command in the terminal (you can directly copy and paste this command):
sudo add-apt-repository ppa:alessandro-strada/ppa sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install google-drive-ocamlfuse Note: The installation process may require a password. Some Linux distributions may not display the entered password. After typing, press Return to continue.</description></item><item><title>Backing up Installed Plugins with Redeb</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-redeb-to-backup-jb-tweaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 04:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-redeb-to-backup-jb-tweaks/</guid><description>A long time ago, the author encountered a situation where a plugin disappeared from another source, preventing them from installing the desired plugin. However, because the plugin was installed on another device, they were able to back up the deb file and install it on the desired device. This article is for those who want to back up their plugins!
Redeb and the backed up deb files (using Zebra as an example)</description></item><item><title>[Fun Test] Test to see if you have a good ear for music!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/are-you-mu-er/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 02:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/are-you-mu-er/</guid><description>This website provides six sets of music in random order, each set containing a 128Kbps MP3/320Kbps MP3/ uncompressed WAV file. The test is to see if you can identify the file with the best sound quality. After making a choice, the correct answer will be revealed.
Friendly reminder:
You can turn up the volume to listen for details. Details can be heard more clearly in the high-pitched parts (so the choice of device is important!</description></item><item><title>AutoDraw: Automatic Drawing!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/autodraw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 02:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/autodraw/</guid><description>(This article was co-edited by SteveYi and 蘿蔔)
A few days ago, during class, SteveYi’s teacher introduced a fun website to the class.
AutoDraw is a website developed by Google. Google actually registered this domain in 1998 (or someone else registered it and then sold it to Google)~ I can’t believe I only found out about this website now!
SteveYi was also curious about how this interesting thing works, so he played around with it and did a little research.</description></item><item><title>Applying for your own ASN through RIPE</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/get-asn-from-ripe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 08:39:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/get-asn-from-ripe/</guid><description>Today we will talk about how to obtain your own ASN through LIR in RIPE.
First of all, some people may wonder:
Why choose RIPE? Isn&amp;rsquo;t APNIC or ARIN a good choice?
The author has two ASNs, one under RIPE and the other under APNIC. When the author makes changes to some whois information, RIPE allows direct web access to make changes, while APNIC requires sending emails&amp;hellip; which is more troublesome (actually it&amp;rsquo;s about the same).</description></item><item><title>Creating Objects in RIPE DataBase</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-object-in-ripe-database/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 08:37:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-object-in-ripe-database/</guid><description>In this article, we will share with you how to register MAINTAINER, PERSON/ROLE, and ORGANIZATION objects in the RIPE DataBase.
These objects are also necessary to register ASN. If you want to apply for ASN, you can refer to this tutorial.
First, we need to register for a RIPE account registration website here.
After completing the registration, we enter the RIPE Database and click &amp;ldquo;Create an Object&amp;rdquo;.
Then we select the first &amp;ldquo;role and maintainer pair&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Building an Internal Network with WireGuard</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-wireguard-to-make-intranet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-wireguard-to-make-intranet/</guid><description>Hi everyone, today I&amp;rsquo;m going to share how to use WireGuard to build an internal network.
Previously, I shared how to install WireGuard on Linux systems. This time, we will use WireGuard to build an internal network.
Why Build an Internal Network? Why does the author call this an &amp;ldquo;internal network&amp;rdquo;? Because the author may be in different places and wants to use this opportunity to add them all to the same LAN.</description></item><item><title>Automatically Correct Time on Windows 10 After Turning on Computer (Wake Up)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ntp-clock-autoset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 15:52:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ntp-clock-autoset/</guid><description>The clock is a very important thing for computers. It is not just about displaying the time in the status bar (or taskbar). If the clock is not correct (deviates too much from the actual time in the real world), it may cause some strange phenomena on the computer, such as: unable to view web pages (certificate issues), and even cause software crashes if the time difference is too great. Timeout login of various programs is also easy to occur when the time deviation is too large.</description></item><item><title>Testing Internal Network Speed via iperf3</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/iperf3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 13:26:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/iperf3/</guid><description>Recently, I replaced my switch and to test the speed of the internal network, I found this tool - iperf3
It is a testing program that supports Windows, Linux, and macOS and is mainly operated through commands. I often use it to test the speed between two different servers in different locations.
So, here&amp;rsquo;s how to install it:
First, go to the iperf3 official website and find the corresponding system (choose Windows for Windows, macOS for macOS, and Linux for Linux).</description></item><item><title>Super useful built-in Spotlight search tips on iOS and macOS</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/apple-spotlight/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 09:02:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/apple-spotlight/</guid><description>Many people have bought iPhones, iPads, iPod touches, or Macs, but they don&amp;rsquo;t know that the built-in Spotlight has many useful features. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look!
How to use Spotlight (the method may be different in earlier versions): On iOS/iPadOS, swipe down on the home screen; on macOS, click on the magnifying glass in the menu bar (top right corner), or press &amp;ldquo;command&amp;rdquo; + &amp;ldquo;space bar&amp;rdquo;.
Note: The search function of Spotlight and Siri has improved with each version, so some older versions may not have certain features.</description></item><item><title>Enhance your Windows gaming experience with Xbox Game Bar</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/xbox-game-bar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/xbox-game-bar/</guid><description>Xbox Game Bar is a feature of Windows 10 that offers recording and streaming, performance monitoring, Spotify music control, and more. It can also be pinned to the screen. The best part is that Game Bar focuses system resources on the game, so players with lower-end computer configurations can enjoy smoother gameplay!
Note: The author used Windows 10 (version 2004) and Xbox Game Bar (version 5.420) as examples. Different versions may look different.</description></item><item><title>Backup and Restore Windows 7 and above PCs</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/windows-backup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 09:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/windows-backup/</guid><description>Mac has a &amp;ldquo;Time Machine&amp;rdquo; that can easily backup the entire computer, and Windows also has a similar function!
In simple terms, it will backup the entire computer, disk drive or folder (depending on the settings). The first backup will be a complete backup, so it will take longer. After the first backup, it will only backup the files that have been modified or created since the last backup to save space and time.</description></item><item><title>Changing Mac Hostname from Terminal</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/mac-hostname/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 08:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/mac-hostname/</guid><description>When we open the terminal, we will see a string of characters that says &amp;ldquo;username@hostname&amp;rdquo;, for example, John@Johns-MacBook.
The hostname can theoretically be changed from the &amp;ldquo;Sharing&amp;rdquo; section in System Preferences. However, for some reason, it may not work on some computers. After searching for a few days, I finally found the answer: we can change the hostname from the terminal.
First, please open the terminal and enter the following command.</description></item><item><title>Speed up email loading on old devices and slow internet with traditional version of Gmail</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/html-gmail/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 15:32:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/html-gmail/</guid><description>The author has an old PC with 1GB of memory and Windows XP, which is suitable for light document use (Windows XP only requires 128MB of memory to operate). It can handle browsing some websites, but some large websites take a long time to load or cannot be used normally. If it is a general article webpage, it can still be managed. The problem is that the author wants to use the Gmail web version to send and receive emails, but it takes nearly a minute to load the standard Gmail webpage when the internet is smooth, and scrolling through emails is a disaster.</description></item><item><title>A Discussion on the Impact of Battery and Performance on Mac Laptops</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macbook-without-a-battery/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 13:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macbook-without-a-battery/</guid><description>As someone who has used PCs since childhood, I only started using a MacBook Pro a few years ago when my family bought one (well, it&amp;rsquo;s not mine, I just borrow it for a long time 😂).
The first laptop I owned was an IBM ThinkPad T43. When I got it, the battery was so old that it was almost useless (it lasted about 3 minutes and 42 seconds from boot to hibernation), so most of the time I removed the battery to reduce the weight, and only installed it when I needed to move between power outlets.</description></item><item><title>Installing macOS Catalina on Unsupported Devices</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macos-catalina-on-unsupport-mac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 10:41:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macos-catalina-on-unsupport-mac/</guid><description>Some computers may still work perfectly fine, but they may be removed from the upgrade list by official sources due to multiple considerations, such as performance, commercial, or functional considerations. Isn&amp;rsquo;t it a shame?
At this time, dosdude1 has solved this problem with the Catalina Patcher.
This is the official support list:
Screenshot from Apple official website
Below is the Catalina Patcher support list, which is consistent with the OS X El Capitan system requirements:</description></item><item><title>Easy Mac Reinstallation with Built-in Recovery Function!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macos-recovery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 07:25:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macos-recovery/</guid><description>There are many reasons why we may need to reinstall our operating system, such as the system becoming slow due to too many installed programs, not wanting to delete programs one by one, or switching to a new disk drive, downgrading from a beta version to a stable release, or unexpected power outages during system upgrades. Mac comes with a useful tool that can help us reinstall the operating system easily.</description></item><item><title>Building interconnectivity between different network segments through BGP</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/bgp-network-peer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 18:56:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/bgp-network-peer/</guid><description>As a child, I often struggled with managing my home network. For example, my home had three floors and three routers. I wanted to make sure that devices connected to each router could communicate with each other. However, if I turned on DHCP Server on each of the routers, the routers would become independent networks that couldn&amp;rsquo;t communicate with each other.
Later, I discovered that by using a bridge to turn one router into a DHCP server and the others into AP or switch, I could achieve the same network and interconnectivity.</description></item><item><title>Experience ChromiumOS with CloudReady and Give Your Old Computer a New Life!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/cloudready/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 15:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/cloudready/</guid><description>Have you ever experienced a situation where your old computer is struggling to handle basic tasks like document processing and web browsing? You may not want to use an outdated operating system that is no longer supported by the official provider, including the browser. In this case, you can download the latest version of CloudReady Home Edition to breathe new life into your computer. It comes with the latest browser and many Web Apps that you can use.</description></item><item><title>How to Use an Android Phone as a Network Connection for a Mac</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/horndis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 07:23:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/horndis/</guid><description>Sometimes, for various reasons, you may not want to use Wi-Fi or a personal hotspot when using the internet, or your computer&amp;rsquo;s wireless network card may be blocked by surrounding objects, or even a black Apple computer may not have a compatible wireless network card. In these cases, using an Android phone as a network receiver is a good idea.
macOS version 10.11 (El Captain) or higher is required, and this article demonstrates using macOS 10.</description></item><item><title>How to Easily Disable Windows 10 Automatic Updates Without Tools</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/no-win10-update/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 14:37:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/no-win10-update/</guid><description>Because Windows 10 updates often take up a lot of storage space and can often cause some inexplicable problems (such as the built-in search function not working), I discovered an effective way to block updates myself.
First, open Start&amp;gt; Settings&amp;gt; Update &amp;amp; Security.
Next, enter Windows Update settings and click on [Advanced options]. If there are available updates, it is recommended to update first before proceeding with the next operation.</description></item><item><title>FRRouting Installation Tutorial</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/frrouting-install/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 13:07:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/frrouting-install/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I last shared anything! Recently, I have been learning about BGP knowledge and testing. Previously, I used Bird1 to broadcast BGP, but when I tried to peer with my friend, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t establish a connection (it was strange, but I could connect with IX). So I uninstalled Bird1 and installed FRRouting instead.
FRRouting is a routing suite that comes from Quagga Fork, and its functionality is also very powerful (its commands are similar to Cisco or Quagga).</description></item><item><title>Method to add real-time lyrics to Spotify or other music software (Android)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/dynamic-lyrics-android/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 10:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/dynamic-lyrics-android/</guid><description>Last time, we introduced the comparison of free memberships among various streaming platforms. As you can see, many platforms have real-time lyrics. However, according to our testing, only Spotify Premium users can use them, and some platforms do not offer lyric services, which is a bit of a shame.
Do you find it inconvenient to listen to free music on Spotify or other platforms without lyrics? If so, follow this article to solve this problem.</description></item><item><title>Add Real-time Lyrics to Spotify (iOS/iPadOS)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/no-premium-spotify-dynamic-lyrics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/no-premium-spotify-dynamic-lyrics/</guid><description>Last time, I introduced a comparison of free memberships for various streaming platforms. You may have noticed that many platforms have real-time lyrics, but according to my testing, only Spotify Premium users can use them, which is a bit of a shame.
Do you want to listen to free music on Spotify, but find it inconvenient to sing without lyrics? This article can help you solve this problem.
This article is for iOS/iPadOS users, while Android users can refer to another article instead.</description></item><item><title>Guide to PVE - Installation</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/pve-install/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 05:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/pve-install/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with virtual machines for some time, but I used VMware Workstation on Windows systems. Later, I had a few idle computers and came across Proxmox VE, an open-source virtualization system. So, let&amp;rsquo;s install and try it out!
Preparation:
Proxmox VE installation disc A high-core and idle computer (otherwise, it will run very slowly) First, let&amp;rsquo;s go to the official website to download the PVE ISO file Official website link.</description></item><item><title>[2020 Latest] Comparison of Major Streaming Platforms with Free Membership</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/free-streaming-music-compare/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 12:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/free-streaming-music-compare/</guid><description>蘿蔔 has been searching for free and easy-to-use streaming music platforms for the past few years, so she has almost used all the common platforms in Taiwan. Therefore, she will introduce each platform to you one by one.
First of all, 蘿蔔 is Taiwanese, so some of the platforms introduced in this article may not be available in other countries or regions, and some platforms may have been updated and this article may not have been updated in time.</description></item><item><title>Automatically categorize LINE chat messages into friends, groups, and official accounts</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/line-xun-xi-fen-lei/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 12:25:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/line-xun-xi-fen-lei/</guid><description>It will be much more convenient to find messages after LINE categorizes them&amp;hellip;
This feature is currently only available on Android, but it should be added to iOS in the near future.
Please make sure that your LINE version is the latest version on Google Play.
First, open LINE and go to the main page.
Next, click on the gear icon in the upper right corner, find LINE Lab, and check the box.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy background playback on Android devices without subscribing to Youtube Music Premium (works for Youtube too!)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-playing-android/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 15:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-playing-android/</guid><description>This guide is primarily demonstrated on an Android phone, although the same method can be applied to Android tablets.
For iOS/iPadOS users, a similar method can be used as described in this post.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get started First, open Youtube Music homepage on Chrome browser (most devices with built-in Google Play services should have it, if not, you can download it here) and do not play any music yet. Click the three dots on the top right corner and check &amp;ldquo;Desktop site&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>No subscription required for Youtube Music Premium to enable background playback on iOS/iPadOS (also works for Youtube!)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-ios/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 14:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-ios/</guid><description>Here we mainly use iPad as an example, but the same method can be applied to iPhone as well. Android devices can also use a similar method, and a tutorial for Android will be posted in the future, so stay tuned for more articles from &amp;ldquo;I am Little Yi&amp;rdquo;!
Update: Android tutorial is available here
Recently, the author has been looking for a good free streaming music service, and found that the Youtube Music App on the computer (actually embedded in the webpage) is quite user-friendly.</description></item><item><title>Adding a New Administrator Account to a Mac When You Forget the Login Credentials</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/iforgot-mac-password/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 05:54:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/iforgot-mac-password/</guid><description>I borrowed an iMac that I used until the holidays, and left it in a safe place before going home (I couldn&amp;rsquo;t take it with me). When I returned after more than a month, I discovered that I had forgotten my password (which sounds unbelievable, but it&amp;rsquo;s true; I couldn&amp;rsquo;t remember my previous password no matter how hard I tried). Fortunately, I had already backed up my data before going home.</description></item><item><title>Use IFTTT to Turn off Wi-Fi When Leaving Home</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ifttt-zhi-dong-guan-wifi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 04:43:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ifttt-zhi-dong-guan-wifi/</guid><description>As I often forget to turn off Wi-Fi when leaving home, I found this method to solve the problem.
First, we need to prepare according to different device types.
For Xiaomi, Redmi, Black Shark, and POCO phone users First, lock and allow IFTTT to self-start and set the power-saving policy to unrestricted from the recent apps. Skip this section if not applicable.
Press and hold the IFTTT preview icon to bring up the menu below.</description></item><item><title>Fixing the issue of Telegram automatically switching back to the default theme when dark mode is enabled on Android</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/telegram-dark-mode-theme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 08:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/telegram-dark-mode-theme/</guid><description>If you have changed the theme on Telegram, you may have noticed that it always switches back to the default dark blue theme when dark mode is enabled on Android.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a solution to this problem:
First, open the side menu and select &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo;.
Next, select &amp;ldquo;Chat Settings&amp;rdquo;.
Finally, find &amp;ldquo;Auto-Night Mode&amp;rdquo; and turn it off.</description></item><item><title>Tips for Improving Mobile Phone Audio Quality</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/yin-zhi-ti-sheng/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 03:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/yin-zhi-ti-sheng/</guid><description>Note: This article also applies to Apple Lightning devices and most USB-C devices, such as Windows computers.
While you may think that the audio quality of your headphones that cost just over $20 is bad, have you overlooked an important detail? Although using headphones from the same brand as your phone may result in better optimization, it cannot be denied that the built-in DAC (an important component that converts digital audio into analog signals and provides them to headphones) of your phone may not be as good as an external DAC.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Tunnel Broker Service (v4 to v6) on Ubuntu System</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/tunnel-broker-bgp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 16:56:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/tunnel-broker-bgp/</guid><description>Introduction I recently obtained an Autonomous System Number (AS Number), along with one /44 and two /48 IPv6 addresses. Coincidentally, I remembered using HE.Net&amp;rsquo;s tunnel broker service before, so I decided to set up a sit tunnel broker service. This article does not explain how to obtain IPv6 addresses, please consult your hosting provider.
This article will use the open source tool - IPv6-in-IPv4 Tunnel.
Configuration tool First, download the tool:</description></item><item><title>Using TeamViewer to Remotely Control Android Phones</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/teamviewer-android/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:09:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/teamviewer-android/</guid><description>Do you often forget to bring your Android phone with you when you need it? TeamViewer can help with that! But you need to remove it from the system&amp;rsquo;s automatic background kill list.
The remote control function is compatible with Android 5~Android 8 (the first time you use it, you may be asked for permission, and you can choose to allow permanently). For Android 9 and above, it is suitable for remote viewing (every time you use it on Android 9 and above, you need to allow it once on your phone, which is more suitable as a tool for wireless display to a computer).</description></item><item><title>Easily Install APK Files to Your Phone with Scrcpy</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/scrcpy-android-apk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 08:52:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/scrcpy-android-apk/</guid><description>First, we need to install Scrcpy and open it.
Installation instructions here
If you are using a Xiaomi phone (if not, skip this part),
go to &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;Additional settings&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;Developer options&amp;rdquo; and allow USB installation.
This action requires a SIM card to be inserted (required by MIUI).
Please have the Finder or File Manager window for the prepared APK file open on the side, and drag the file into the Scrcpy window.</description></item><item><title>Using Scrcpy to Control Your Android Phone from Your Computer</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/scrcpy-android/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 15:41:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/scrcpy-android/</guid><description>Introduction: Due to a sudden breakdown of the screen of my phone, the liquid crystal display (LCD) would display but with no backlight, making it difficult to view the screen. However, I still needed to use the phone to transfer important data and test Android programs. Therefore, I had to figure out a way to operate it! (As I currently use an iPhone)
(Screen can only be vaguely seen under intense light)</description></item><item><title>Using WireGuard on Linux</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/how-to-use-wireguard/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 11:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/how-to-use-wireguard/</guid><description>WireGuard is a point-to-point encryption network. I have been using it to manage/connect all my cloud servers.
Today, let&amp;rsquo;s share how to use WireGuard!
Install WireGuard Basically, the WireGuard Install Page provides complete installation methods and commands for various versions, so you can refer to it directly.
Create WireGuard Profile First, go to the WireGuard installation folder. If it does not exist, please create it.
cd /etc/wireguard Use the command to generate a public and private key, and use &amp;ldquo;cat&amp;rdquo; to view the contents of the public and private keys.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Cloud Identity account</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-cloud-identity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 20:35:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-cloud-identity/</guid><description>First, go to the Cloud Identity registration page and click on the next page button.
Then enter your company name (you can enter any name), number of employees (choose any number) and treat it as a team.
Select your location (once set, it cannot be changed), but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter.
Set up your current email address (some registration emails will be sent here).
Enter the domain you want to set up (cannot be used for other G Suite services).</description></item><item><title>Delete G Suite organization</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/delete-gsuite/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 18:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/delete-gsuite/</guid><description>Previously, I shared with you the way to register a G Suite account. Recently, I wanted to delete the G Suite organization of the Cloud Identity free version.
Since I have never deleted a G Suite organization before, I searched for information and roughly sorted out the deletion method.
Important reminder: Before deletion, please cancel the contractual authorization and delete all GCP projects. After deletion, all organization data will be cleared.</description></item><item><title>Backblaze B2 now supports S3 API!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2-compatible-s3-api/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 03:08:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2-compatible-s3-api/</guid><description>A few days ago, when I opened Backblaze, I saw a big line of text:
That&amp;rsquo;s right! Backblaze B2 now supports the S3 API!
The S3 API is currently the most popular protocol in the market, and many hardware and software are compatible.
Backblaze B2 is a great cloud storage option with a low cost advantage.
How to use the S3 API If the storage bucket was created before May 4, 2020, you will need to create a new one and move your files into it (we recommend using Rclone, which will automatically support B2 Copy File).</description></item><item><title>Backblaze B2: Affordable Cloud Data Storage Service</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2/</guid><description>When I was learning how to build a website, I considered a problem!
If my traffic suddenly increased and I had more articles, would my image storage and bandwidth also increase?
So I searched for some object storage services online and found a cheap object storage provider - Backblaze.
What is Object Storage? Object storage is a type of data storage where each data unit is stored as a discrete unit called an object.</description></item><item><title>Hosting Static Websites with Github - Github Pages</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/github-static-website/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 14:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/github-static-website/</guid><description>First, go to Github and click on the green New button on the left.
Enter a Repository name (customizable)
Choose Public or Private
Click on Create Repository
Now you have created a Repository!
Next, we need to download Github Desktop to easily upload the website source files.
Click on Download for macOS (or Download for Windows for Windows)
After downloading, sign in to your Github account (Sign in to Github.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Custom Email Domain with Mailgun and Gmail</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/mailgun-gmail-custom-domain-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 12:48:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/mailgun-gmail-custom-domain-email/</guid><description>As a child, I was always curious about the domain name of the sender in an email. Later, after getting involved in website development, I registered many domains (currently having about 6 domains), and gradually understood the doubts I had as a child.
Today, I will share with you the method of setting up custom email domain with Mailgun and Gmail!
First, register with Mailgun, which offers 5000 free emails by default.</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare New Service Spectrum Setup Tutorial</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/hot-to-set-cloudflare-spectrum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 08:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/hot-to-set-cloudflare-spectrum/</guid><description>This morning when I opened Facebook, I found that Cloudflare has launched a new service - Spectrum. It is currently available to all paid users, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know if there will be a chance to open it to free customers in the future. Official blog link: https://cfl.re/3efcOhv
Coincidentally, I have several domains that use the Plesk Plus service (this service has been discontinued), which is considered Cloudflare Pro version, so I can also activate this feature!</description></item><item><title>Announce IPv6 on Vultr with BIRD</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-bird6-broadcast-ipv6-vultr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 02:21:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-bird6-broadcast-ipv6-vultr/</guid><description>It is recommended to refer to the article Building an Internal Network with Friends via BGP on January 24, 2021.
This time, let&amp;rsquo;s share how to broadcast IP on Vultr!
Setting the AS number and IP prefix First, we need to activate the BGP function! Click here to go to the Vultr BGP page After entering this page, click Get Started.
Select I have my own IP space and I have own my ASN (if there is no ASN, you do not need to select it)</description></item><item><title>Forward Missed Calls and SMS to LINE Using IFTTT</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ifttt-forward-to-line/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 04:56:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ifttt-forward-to-line/</guid><description>Preparation
First, you need to register or log in to IFTTT (ifttt.com)
Next, it will recommend an IFTTT example, click X to skip it.
Enter LINE in the search bar in the upper left corner.
Then select LINE in the Services.
Click on Connect and log in to your account.
Please log in to the account that will receive the notifications!
Then click on the green Confirm button to link the account.</description></item><item><title>[Tutorial] AWS Route 53 DNS Hosting</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/aws-route53/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 14:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/aws-route53/</guid><description>Since 2017, after registering my first domain, DNS hosting has always been a part of my research!
Today, I want to recommend DNS hosting service Route 53 launched by AWS.
Prerequisites:
AWS account
Domain
Create Hosted Zone First, enter the AWS console and search for Route 53.
Then click on Hosted Zones at the top left.
Click on Create Hosted Zone on the upper left, and then enter your domain name on the right.</description></item><item><title>Buying a domain on Gandi</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/register-domain-at-gandi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:40:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/register-domain-at-gandi/</guid><description>Previously, I shared the process of transferring a domain from Google to Gandi click here to read the article. In this post, I will share the process of buying a domain on Gandi!
Prerequisites: Money (for the domain registration fee)
First, we open Gandi&amp;rsquo;s official website.
Search for the domain you want and add it to your shopping cart.
Then you can proceed to checkout.
Gandi supports many payment methods: credit card, UnionPay, PayPal, bank transfer, Bitcoin.</description></item><item><title>Transferring Domain from Google Domains to Gandi</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/transfer-domain-from-google-to-gandi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 02:55:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/transfer-domain-from-google-to-gandi/</guid><description>In the past few days, I received a notification email from Google Domains reminding me that my domain would need to be renewed soon.
Coincidentally, I had planned to transfer all my domains to Gandi for unified management. So, I&amp;rsquo;ll take this opportunity to share how to transfer a domain out/in.
Preparation:
Registered domain (the one to be transferred out) Money (required for domain renewal when transferred to another registrar) First, go to Google Domains to unlock the domain and obtain the transfer authorization code.</description></item><item><title>Applying for a G Suite account</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/register-gsuite/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/register-gsuite/</guid><description>I believe most of you have used Gmail before. Today, we want to introduce G Suite, an enterprise service launched by Google. However, individual users can also apply for it!
Preparation: Domain (not necessary) Credit card/Debit card
Registration process: First, let&amp;rsquo;s open the G Suite official website (https://gsuite.google.com)
Next, click &amp;ldquo;Start Free Trial&amp;rdquo;
Enter the company name (or any name you want) on the top. Choose the number of employees (I selected 1).</description></item><item><title>Setting up Custom Domain Name for Backblaze B2 with Cloudflare Workers</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/b2-cfworkers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/b2-cfworkers/</guid><description>When building a website, it is important to consider issues related to image storage and traffic.
Initially, I stored the images and website on the same web server, but later found that the server space was often insufficient (because the system automatically backed up, causing insufficient space).
Later, I placed the images on OneDrive Business Edition and used it with OneList, but since it was an unofficial API, when the API request rate was too fast, the images failed to load.</description></item><item><title>Downgrade 32-bit iOS Devices to 8.4.1 without Computer and SHSH</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backtoios841/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 13:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backtoios841/</guid><description>Sometimes there may be problems with Apple, causing various problems. If there are any errors, please try again another day.
Apple&amp;rsquo;s vulnerabilities are not very stable. I tried three times in one day and couldn&amp;rsquo;t use them. I succeeded once another day. This is a bit of luck.
If the iOS device is slow, downgrading will be smoother
(A5 devices are very noticeable, while A6 and A6X devices are not much different but still a bit faster)</description></item><item><title>Windows 10 DD Image specifically for GCP</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/gcp-windows-dd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 15:07:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/gcp-windows-dd/</guid><description>Recently, in order to use VPS on GCP, I created a Windows DD image during a period of time. The images are:
Traditional Chinese version of Windows 10 Workstation Professional Edition English version of Windows 10 Workstation Professional Edition (not uploaded yet) The image has the following features:
Integrated with Virtio driver and Google Virtio Ethernet Adapter network card driver, suitable for GCP VPS servers Unattended installation without VNC interaction. Once DD is completed, you can remotely log in to the desktop Made based on VOL version, so the system can be activated by KMS method Turn on Windows Remote Desktop Traditional Chinese version Download link: http://static-a1.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/configure-ex2200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/configure-ex2200/</guid><description>Basic Configuration and Unboxing of EX2200 Recently, I had the opportunity to use a Juniper L3 Switch - EX2200-C. In this article, I will be discussing the basic configuration and unboxing of the device.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/linux-tunnel-over-ipsec/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/linux-tunnel-over-ipsec/</guid><description>Setting up IPSec Point-to-Point Tunnel in Linux Environment Recently, I acquired a new server that requires IPSec encryption to be set up in its network environment. Otherwise, the GRE Tunnel packets will be visible.
To set up IPSec, run the following command in the Linux terminal:
apt install charon-systemd libcharon-extra-plugins libstrongswan-extra-plugins This will install the necessary plugins for IPSec. The next step is to configure the IPSec tunnel, which involves setting up BGP and configuring the internet routing protocols.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/usb-reverse-tethering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/usb-reverse-tethering/</guid><description>Using USB to Send Internet Connection from Computer to Phone (USB Reverse Tethering) This tutorial demonstrates using a phone with Android 5.0.2 and damaged Wi-Fi and Bluetooth features, paired with Windows 10.
Please note: It&amp;rsquo;s not guaranteed that every phone is compatible, and even if it is, some apps may not recognize this type of connection (they usually only recognize mobile data and Wi-Fi connections).
This article focuses on the Windows platform, so other operating systems will not be discussed, but they should be similar.</description></item><item><title>About Tsung-Yi</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/about/</guid><description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Tsung-Yi Yu, widely recognized as SteveYi or &amp;ldquo;小易&amp;rdquo;.
At the heart of my professional journey lies a deep fascination with internet governance research, cutting-edge internet technologies, and virtualization design. Over the years, my dedication has led me to immerse myself in pivotal events both locally and globally. I&amp;rsquo;ve been privileged to attend, and in many cases present at, significant conferences including APNIC 54/56, the ICANN APAC-TWNIC Engagement Forum, and the Taiwan Internet Governance Forum (TWIGF).</description></item><item><title>APAN Fellowship Program</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/apan-fellowship/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/apan-fellowship/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m very glad to be able to participate in this program. I hope that I can contribute to the APAN community and to the APAN Foundation.
Attending APRICOT 2022 / APNIC 53 Based on the COVID-19, APRICOT 2022 conference are 100% online conference.
Before attending this conference, I need to register on their website. Since the conference is online, APNIC does not charge for the tickets.
There has 886 registered participants (Include me).</description></item><item><title>Multi Language Site is now Enabled!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/hello_world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/hello_world/</guid><description>Today, I have now enabled my multi languages site.
I still translate some old posts into English, please wait :)
You should see both languages version posts soon.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Welcome to &amp;ldquo;CoolEasy&amp;rdquo; (hereinafter referred to as this website). In order to ensure that you can use the various services and information of this website with peace of mind, we hereby explain the privacy protection policy of this website to protect your rights and interests. Please read the following contents carefully:
I. Scope of application of privacy protection policy The content of the privacy protection policy includes how this website handles personal identification information collected when you use website services.</description></item></channel></rss>