<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>website logs on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/website-logs/</link><description>Recent content in website logs on SteveYi's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>tw</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/website-logs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Backblaze B2: Affordable Cloud Data Storage Service</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2/</guid><description>When I was learning how to build a website, I considered a problem!
If my traffic suddenly increased and I had more articles, would my image storage and bandwidth also increase?
So I searched for some object storage services online and found a cheap object storage provider - Backblaze.
What is Object Storage? Object storage is a type of data storage where each data unit is stored as a discrete unit called an object.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Custom Domain Name for Backblaze B2 with Cloudflare Workers</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/b2-cfworkers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/b2-cfworkers/</guid><description>When building a website, it is important to consider issues related to image storage and traffic.
Initially, I stored the images and website on the same web server, but later found that the server space was often insufficient (because the system automatically backed up, causing insufficient space).
Later, I placed the images on OneDrive Business Edition and used it with OneList, but since it was an unofficial API, when the API request rate was too fast, the images failed to load.</description></item></channel></rss>