<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>life hacks on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/life-hacks/</link><description>Recent content in life hacks on SteveYi's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>tw</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 12:25:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/life-hacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Easy integration with Google Drive in Linux environment</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/linux-mount-googledrive-not-required-brain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 12:25:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/linux-mount-googledrive-not-required-brain/</guid><description>This tutorial uses the software google-drive-ocamlfuse and the demonstration is based on the Ubuntu-based Zorin OS 15.2 system.
First, you need to add the software source. Please enter the following command in the terminal (you can directly copy and paste this command):
sudo add-apt-repository ppa:alessandro-strada/ppa sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install google-drive-ocamlfuse Note: The installation process may require a password. Some Linux distributions may not display the entered password. After typing, press Return to continue.</description></item><item><title>[Fun Test] Test to see if you have a good ear for music!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/are-you-mu-er/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 02:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/are-you-mu-er/</guid><description>This website provides six sets of music in random order, each set containing a 128Kbps MP3/320Kbps MP3/ uncompressed WAV file. The test is to see if you can identify the file with the best sound quality. After making a choice, the correct answer will be revealed.
Friendly reminder:
You can turn up the volume to listen for details. Details can be heard more clearly in the high-pitched parts (so the choice of device is important!</description></item><item><title>AutoDraw: Automatic Drawing!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/autodraw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 02:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/autodraw/</guid><description>(This article was co-edited by SteveYi and 蘿蔔)
A few days ago, during class, SteveYi’s teacher introduced a fun website to the class.
AutoDraw is a website developed by Google. Google actually registered this domain in 1998 (or someone else registered it and then sold it to Google)~ I can’t believe I only found out about this website now!
SteveYi was also curious about how this interesting thing works, so he played around with it and did a little research.</description></item><item><title>Super useful built-in Spotlight search tips on iOS and macOS</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/apple-spotlight/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 09:02:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/apple-spotlight/</guid><description>Many people have bought iPhones, iPads, iPod touches, or Macs, but they don&amp;rsquo;t know that the built-in Spotlight has many useful features. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look!
How to use Spotlight (the method may be different in earlier versions): On iOS/iPadOS, swipe down on the home screen; on macOS, click on the magnifying glass in the menu bar (top right corner), or press &amp;ldquo;command&amp;rdquo; + &amp;ldquo;space bar&amp;rdquo;.
Note: The search function of Spotlight and Siri has improved with each version, so some older versions may not have certain features.</description></item><item><title>Enhance your Windows gaming experience with Xbox Game Bar</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/xbox-game-bar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/xbox-game-bar/</guid><description>Xbox Game Bar is a feature of Windows 10 that offers recording and streaming, performance monitoring, Spotify music control, and more. It can also be pinned to the screen. The best part is that Game Bar focuses system resources on the game, so players with lower-end computer configurations can enjoy smoother gameplay!
Note: The author used Windows 10 (version 2004) and Xbox Game Bar (version 5.420) as examples. Different versions may look different.</description></item><item><title>Installing macOS Catalina on Unsupported Devices</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macos-catalina-on-unsupport-mac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 10:41:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macos-catalina-on-unsupport-mac/</guid><description>Some computers may still work perfectly fine, but they may be removed from the upgrade list by official sources due to multiple considerations, such as performance, commercial, or functional considerations. Isn&amp;rsquo;t it a shame?
At this time, dosdude1 has solved this problem with the Catalina Patcher.
This is the official support list:
Screenshot from Apple official website
Below is the Catalina Patcher support list, which is consistent with the OS X El Capitan system requirements:</description></item><item><title>Easy Mac Reinstallation with Built-in Recovery Function!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macos-recovery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 07:25:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macos-recovery/</guid><description>There are many reasons why we may need to reinstall our operating system, such as the system becoming slow due to too many installed programs, not wanting to delete programs one by one, or switching to a new disk drive, downgrading from a beta version to a stable release, or unexpected power outages during system upgrades. Mac comes with a useful tool that can help us reinstall the operating system easily.</description></item><item><title>Experience ChromiumOS with CloudReady and Give Your Old Computer a New Life!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/cloudready/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 15:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/cloudready/</guid><description>Have you ever experienced a situation where your old computer is struggling to handle basic tasks like document processing and web browsing? You may not want to use an outdated operating system that is no longer supported by the official provider, including the browser. In this case, you can download the latest version of CloudReady Home Edition to breathe new life into your computer. It comes with the latest browser and many Web Apps that you can use.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy background playback on Android devices without subscribing to Youtube Music Premium (works for Youtube too!)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-playing-android/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 15:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-playing-android/</guid><description>This guide is primarily demonstrated on an Android phone, although the same method can be applied to Android tablets.
For iOS/iPadOS users, a similar method can be used as described in this post.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get started First, open Youtube Music homepage on Chrome browser (most devices with built-in Google Play services should have it, if not, you can download it here) and do not play any music yet. Click the three dots on the top right corner and check &amp;ldquo;Desktop site&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Fixing the issue of Telegram automatically switching back to the default theme when dark mode is enabled on Android</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/telegram-dark-mode-theme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 08:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/telegram-dark-mode-theme/</guid><description>If you have changed the theme on Telegram, you may have noticed that it always switches back to the default dark blue theme when dark mode is enabled on Android.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a solution to this problem:
First, open the side menu and select &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo;.
Next, select &amp;ldquo;Chat Settings&amp;rdquo;.
Finally, find &amp;ldquo;Auto-Night Mode&amp;rdquo; and turn it off.</description></item></channel></rss>