<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Network on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/network/</link><description>Recent content in Network on SteveYi's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 13:20:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setting up NAT on iptables</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/iptables_nat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 13:20:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/iptables_nat/</guid><description>Recently, Xiaoyi installed Ubuntu 20.04 on a computer at home and used it as a soft router.
But Xiaoyi found that the computer couldn&amp;rsquo;t connect to the internet!
After using mtr to trace the route, we found that the route could not go beyond the Gateway. So we captured packets on the router and found that our internal IP was sent to the ISP, but there was no response.
If the ISP hasn&amp;rsquo;t configured it properly, it can easily lead to IP Spoofing.</description></item><item><title>Become a MANRS participant!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/join-manrs-as-participants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:03:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/join-manrs-as-participants/</guid><description>At the end of last year, I submitted an application for MANRS for SteveYi Network Service. At the beginning of this year, we passed the review and officially became a participant in MANRS! Our member introduction can be found here: https://www.manrs.org/isps/participants/entry/1484/
So, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about how we implement MANRS policies.
MANRS has four main policies, which are:
Prevent propagation of incorrect routing information Prevent traffic with incorrect spoofed source IP addresses Promote coordination between network operators Facilitate global operational communication and coordination</description></item><item><title>Building an Internal Network with Friends using BGP</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/make-internal-network-by-bgp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/make-internal-network-by-bgp/</guid><description>Hi! Long time no see!
In early 2020, I obtained my first ASN number - AS209557
I also used IP Addresses defined by RFC 1918, and with some friends, I built a large internal network using BGP and Internet tunnels.
So let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
First, we use Ubuntu 20.04 to establish a tunnel and establish BGP peerings with others.
Usually, I use GRE, SIT, or WireGuard.
Among them, GRE or SIT tunnels are non-encrypted tunnels that can be viewed on the public network.</description></item></channel></rss>