<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Domain on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/domain/</link><description>Recent content in Domain on SteveYi's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 05:33:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/domain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guide to PVE - Installation</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/pve-install/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 05:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/pve-install/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with virtual machines for some time, but I used VMware Workstation on Windows systems. Later, I had a few idle computers and came across Proxmox VE, an open-source virtualization system. So, let&amp;rsquo;s install and try it out!
Preparation:
Proxmox VE installation disc A high-core and idle computer (otherwise, it will run very slowly) First, let&amp;rsquo;s go to the official website to download the PVE ISO file Official website link.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Tunnel Broker Service (v4 to v6) on Ubuntu System</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/tunnel-broker-bgp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 16:56:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/tunnel-broker-bgp/</guid><description>Introduction I recently obtained an Autonomous System Number (AS Number), along with one /44 and two /48 IPv6 addresses. Coincidentally, I remembered using HE.Net&amp;rsquo;s tunnel broker service before, so I decided to set up a sit tunnel broker service. This article does not explain how to obtain IPv6 addresses, please consult your hosting provider.
This article will use the open source tool - IPv6-in-IPv4 Tunnel.
Configuration tool First, download the tool:</description></item><item><title>Creating a Cloud Identity account</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-cloud-identity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 20:35:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-cloud-identity/</guid><description>First, go to the Cloud Identity registration page and click on the next page button.
Then enter your company name (you can enter any name), number of employees (choose any number) and treat it as a team.
Select your location (once set, it cannot be changed), but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter.
Set up your current email address (some registration emails will be sent here).
Enter the domain you want to set up (cannot be used for other G Suite services).</description></item><item><title>Delete G Suite organization</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/delete-gsuite/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 18:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/delete-gsuite/</guid><description>Previously, I shared with you the way to register a G Suite account. Recently, I wanted to delete the G Suite organization of the Cloud Identity free version.
Since I have never deleted a G Suite organization before, I searched for information and roughly sorted out the deletion method.
Important reminder: Before deletion, please cancel the contractual authorization and delete all GCP projects. After deletion, all organization data will be cleared.</description></item><item><title>Backblaze B2 now supports S3 API!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2-compatible-s3-api/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 03:08:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2-compatible-s3-api/</guid><description>A few days ago, when I opened Backblaze, I saw a big line of text:
That&amp;rsquo;s right! Backblaze B2 now supports the S3 API!
The S3 API is currently the most popular protocol in the market, and many hardware and software are compatible.
Backblaze B2 is a great cloud storage option with a low cost advantage.
How to use the S3 API If the storage bucket was created before May 4, 2020, you will need to create a new one and move your files into it (we recommend using Rclone, which will automatically support B2 Copy File).</description></item><item><title>Hosting Static Websites with Github - Github Pages</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/github-static-website/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 14:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/github-static-website/</guid><description>First, go to Github and click on the green New button on the left.
Enter a Repository name (customizable)
Choose Public or Private
Click on Create Repository
Now you have created a Repository!
Next, we need to download Github Desktop to easily upload the website source files.
Click on Download for macOS (or Download for Windows for Windows)
After downloading, sign in to your Github account (Sign in to Github.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Custom Email Domain with Mailgun and Gmail</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/mailgun-gmail-custom-domain-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 12:48:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/mailgun-gmail-custom-domain-email/</guid><description>As a child, I was always curious about the domain name of the sender in an email. Later, after getting involved in website development, I registered many domains (currently having about 6 domains), and gradually understood the doubts I had as a child.
Today, I will share with you the method of setting up custom email domain with Mailgun and Gmail!
First, register with Mailgun, which offers 5000 free emails by default.</description></item><item><title>[Tutorial] AWS Route 53 DNS Hosting</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/aws-route53/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 14:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/aws-route53/</guid><description>Since 2017, after registering my first domain, DNS hosting has always been a part of my research!
Today, I want to recommend DNS hosting service Route 53 launched by AWS.
Prerequisites:
AWS account
Domain
Create Hosted Zone First, enter the AWS console and search for Route 53.
Then click on Hosted Zones at the top left.
Click on Create Hosted Zone on the upper left, and then enter your domain name on the right.</description></item><item><title>Buying a domain on Gandi</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/register-domain-at-gandi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:40:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/register-domain-at-gandi/</guid><description>Previously, I shared the process of transferring a domain from Google to Gandi click here to read the article. In this post, I will share the process of buying a domain on Gandi!
Prerequisites: Money (for the domain registration fee)
First, we open Gandi&amp;rsquo;s official website.
Search for the domain you want and add it to your shopping cart.
Then you can proceed to checkout.
Gandi supports many payment methods: credit card, UnionPay, PayPal, bank transfer, Bitcoin.</description></item></channel></rss>