<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Internet on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/internet/</link><description>Recent content in Internet on SteveYi's Blog</description><image><url>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</url><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 05:35:35 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using AS-SET to build filters</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-as-set-to-make-filter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 05:35:35 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-as-set-to-make-filter/</guid><description>Recently, in order to establish BGP Peers with some friends who are new to the field, I also taught them how to use AS-SET for filtering.
What is AS-SET AS-SET is an object that can add ASN and AS-SET.
Usually used to filter routes exchanged through the BGP protocol. (such as BGP Peer Neighbor, Internet Exchange Route Server, etc.)
We usually query all Route Objects in this AS-SET through Whois and recursion.</description></item><item><title>Easy integration with Google Drive in Linux environment</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/linux-mount-googledrive-not-required-brain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 12:25:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/linux-mount-googledrive-not-required-brain/</guid><description>This tutorial uses the software google-drive-ocamlfuse and the demonstration is based on the Ubuntu-based Zorin OS 15.2 system.
First, you need to add the software source. Please enter the following command in the terminal (you can directly copy and paste this command):
sudo add-apt-repository ppa:alessandro-strada/ppa sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install google-drive-ocamlfuse Note: The installation process may require a password. Some Linux distributions may not display the entered password. After typing, press Return to continue.</description></item><item><title>Applying for your own ASN through RIPE</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/get-asn-from-ripe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 08:39:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/get-asn-from-ripe/</guid><description>Today we will talk about how to obtain your own ASN through LIR in RIPE.
First of all, some people may wonder:
Why choose RIPE? Isn&amp;rsquo;t APNIC or ARIN a good choice?
The author has two ASNs, one under RIPE and the other under APNIC. When the author makes changes to some whois information, RIPE allows direct web access to make changes, while APNIC requires sending emails&amp;hellip; which is more troublesome (actually it&amp;rsquo;s about the same).</description></item><item><title>Creating Objects in RIPE DataBase</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-object-in-ripe-database/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 08:37:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-object-in-ripe-database/</guid><description>In this article, we will share with you how to register MAINTAINER, PERSON/ROLE, and ORGANIZATION objects in the RIPE DataBase.
These objects are also necessary to register ASN. If you want to apply for ASN, you can refer to this tutorial.
First, we need to register for a RIPE account registration website here.
After completing the registration, we enter the RIPE Database and click &amp;ldquo;Create an Object&amp;rdquo;.
Then we select the first &amp;ldquo;role and maintainer pair&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>