<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>server on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/server/</link><description>Recent content in server on SteveYi's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 18:31:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building an Internal Network with WireGuard</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-wireguard-to-make-intranet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-wireguard-to-make-intranet/</guid><description>Hi everyone, today I&amp;rsquo;m going to share how to use WireGuard to build an internal network.
Previously, I shared how to install WireGuard on Linux systems. This time, we will use WireGuard to build an internal network.
Why Build an Internal Network? Why does the author call this an &amp;ldquo;internal network&amp;rdquo;? Because the author may be in different places and wants to use this opportunity to add them all to the same LAN.</description></item><item><title>FRRouting Installation Tutorial</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/frrouting-install/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 13:07:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/frrouting-install/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I last shared anything! Recently, I have been learning about BGP knowledge and testing. Previously, I used Bird1 to broadcast BGP, but when I tried to peer with my friend, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t establish a connection (it was strange, but I could connect with IX). So I uninstalled Bird1 and installed FRRouting instead.
FRRouting is a routing suite that comes from Quagga Fork, and its functionality is also very powerful (its commands are similar to Cisco or Quagga).</description></item><item><title>Guide to PVE - Installation</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/pve-install/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 05:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/pve-install/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with virtual machines for some time, but I used VMware Workstation on Windows systems. Later, I had a few idle computers and came across Proxmox VE, an open-source virtualization system. So, let&amp;rsquo;s install and try it out!
Preparation:
Proxmox VE installation disc A high-core and idle computer (otherwise, it will run very slowly) First, let&amp;rsquo;s go to the official website to download the PVE ISO file Official website link.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Tunnel Broker Service (v4 to v6) on Ubuntu System</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/tunnel-broker-bgp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 16:56:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/tunnel-broker-bgp/</guid><description>Introduction I recently obtained an Autonomous System Number (AS Number), along with one /44 and two /48 IPv6 addresses. Coincidentally, I remembered using HE.Net&amp;rsquo;s tunnel broker service before, so I decided to set up a sit tunnel broker service. This article does not explain how to obtain IPv6 addresses, please consult your hosting provider.
This article will use the open source tool - IPv6-in-IPv4 Tunnel.
Configuration tool First, download the tool:</description></item><item><title>Using WireGuard on Linux</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/how-to-use-wireguard/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 11:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/how-to-use-wireguard/</guid><description>WireGuard is a point-to-point encryption network. I have been using it to manage/connect all my cloud servers.
Today, let&amp;rsquo;s share how to use WireGuard!
Install WireGuard Basically, the WireGuard Install Page provides complete installation methods and commands for various versions, so you can refer to it directly.
Create WireGuard Profile First, go to the WireGuard installation folder. If it does not exist, please create it.
cd /etc/wireguard Use the command to generate a public and private key, and use &amp;ldquo;cat&amp;rdquo; to view the contents of the public and private keys.</description></item><item><title>Backblaze B2 now supports S3 API!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2-compatible-s3-api/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 03:08:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2-compatible-s3-api/</guid><description>A few days ago, when I opened Backblaze, I saw a big line of text:
That&amp;rsquo;s right! Backblaze B2 now supports the S3 API!
The S3 API is currently the most popular protocol in the market, and many hardware and software are compatible.
Backblaze B2 is a great cloud storage option with a low cost advantage.
How to use the S3 API If the storage bucket was created before May 4, 2020, you will need to create a new one and move your files into it (we recommend using Rclone, which will automatically support B2 Copy File).</description></item><item><title>Cloudflare New Service Spectrum Setup Tutorial</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/hot-to-set-cloudflare-spectrum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 08:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/hot-to-set-cloudflare-spectrum/</guid><description>This morning when I opened Facebook, I found that Cloudflare has launched a new service - Spectrum. It is currently available to all paid users, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know if there will be a chance to open it to free customers in the future. Official blog link: https://cfl.re/3efcOhv
Coincidentally, I have several domains that use the Plesk Plus service (this service has been discontinued), which is considered Cloudflare Pro version, so I can also activate this feature!</description></item><item><title>Announce IPv6 on Vultr with BIRD</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-bird6-broadcast-ipv6-vultr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 02:21:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-bird6-broadcast-ipv6-vultr/</guid><description>It is recommended to refer to the article Building an Internal Network with Friends via BGP on January 24, 2021.
This time, let&amp;rsquo;s share how to broadcast IP on Vultr!
Setting the AS number and IP prefix First, we need to activate the BGP function! Click here to go to the Vultr BGP page After entering this page, click Get Started.
Select I have my own IP space and I have own my ASN (if there is no ASN, you do not need to select it)</description></item><item><title>Setting up Custom Domain Name for Backblaze B2 with Cloudflare Workers</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/b2-cfworkers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/b2-cfworkers/</guid><description>When building a website, it is important to consider issues related to image storage and traffic.
Initially, I stored the images and website on the same web server, but later found that the server space was often insufficient (because the system automatically backed up, causing insufficient space).
Later, I placed the images on OneDrive Business Edition and used it with OneList, but since it was an unofficial API, when the API request rate was too fast, the images failed to load.</description></item><item><title>Windows 10 DD Image specifically for GCP</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/gcp-windows-dd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 15:07:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/gcp-windows-dd/</guid><description>Recently, in order to use VPS on GCP, I created a Windows DD image during a period of time. The images are:
Traditional Chinese version of Windows 10 Workstation Professional Edition English version of Windows 10 Workstation Professional Edition (not uploaded yet) The image has the following features:
Integrated with Virtio driver and Google Virtio Ethernet Adapter network card driver, suitable for GCP VPS servers Unattended installation without VNC interaction. Once DD is completed, you can remotely log in to the desktop Made based on VOL version, so the system can be activated by KMS method Turn on Windows Remote Desktop Traditional Chinese version Download link: http://static-a1.</description></item></channel></rss>