<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Free resources on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/free-resources/</link><description>Recent content in Free resources on SteveYi's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>tw</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 12:25:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/free-resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Easy integration with Google Drive in Linux environment</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/linux-mount-googledrive-not-required-brain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 12:25:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/linux-mount-googledrive-not-required-brain/</guid><description>This tutorial uses the software google-drive-ocamlfuse and the demonstration is based on the Ubuntu-based Zorin OS 15.2 system.
First, you need to add the software source. Please enter the following command in the terminal (you can directly copy and paste this command):
sudo add-apt-repository ppa:alessandro-strada/ppa sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install google-drive-ocamlfuse Note: The installation process may require a password. Some Linux distributions may not display the entered password. After typing, press Return to continue.</description></item><item><title>[Fun Test] Test to see if you have a good ear for music!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/are-you-mu-er/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 02:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/are-you-mu-er/</guid><description>This website provides six sets of music in random order, each set containing a 128Kbps MP3/320Kbps MP3/ uncompressed WAV file. The test is to see if you can identify the file with the best sound quality. After making a choice, the correct answer will be revealed.
Friendly reminder:
You can turn up the volume to listen for details. Details can be heard more clearly in the high-pitched parts (so the choice of device is important!</description></item><item><title>AutoDraw: Automatic Drawing!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/autodraw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 02:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/autodraw/</guid><description>(This article was co-edited by SteveYi and Carrot)
A few days ago, during class, SteveYi’s teacher introduced a fun website to the class.
AutoDraw is a website developed by Google. Google actually registered this domain in 1998 (or someone else registered it and then sold it to Google)~ I can’t believe I only found out about this website now!
SteveYi was also curious about how this interesting thing works, so he played around with it and did a little research.</description></item><item><title>Automatically Correct Time on Windows 10 After Turning on Computer (Wake Up)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ntp-clock-autoset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 15:52:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ntp-clock-autoset/</guid><description>The clock is a very important thing for computers. It is not just about displaying the time in the status bar (or taskbar). If the clock is not correct (deviates too much from the actual time in the real world), it may cause some strange phenomena on the computer, such as: unable to view web pages (certificate issues), and even cause software crashes if the time difference is too great. Timeout login of various programs is also easy to occur when the time deviation is too large.</description></item><item><title>Enhance your Windows gaming experience with Xbox Game Bar</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/xbox-game-bar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/xbox-game-bar/</guid><description>Xbox Game Bar is a feature of Windows 10 that offers recording and streaming, performance monitoring, Spotify music control, and more. It can also be pinned to the screen. The best part is that Game Bar focuses system resources on the game, so players with lower-end computer configurations can enjoy smoother gameplay!
Note: The author used Windows 10 (version 2004) and Xbox Game Bar (version 5.420) as examples. Different versions may look different.</description></item><item><title>Backup and Restore Windows 7 and above PCs</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/windows-backup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 09:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/windows-backup/</guid><description>Mac has a &amp;ldquo;Time Machine&amp;rdquo; that can easily backup the entire computer, and Windows also has a similar function!
In simple terms, it will backup the entire computer, disk drive or folder (depending on the settings). The first backup will be a complete backup, so it will take longer. After the first backup, it will only backup the files that have been modified or created since the last backup to save space and time.</description></item><item><title>Speed up email loading on old devices and slow internet with traditional version of Gmail</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/html-gmail/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 15:32:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/html-gmail/</guid><description>The author has an old PC with 1GB of memory and Windows XP, which is suitable for light document use (Windows XP only requires 128MB of memory to operate). It can handle browsing some websites, but some large websites take a long time to load or cannot be used normally. If it is a general article webpage, it can still be managed. The problem is that the author wants to use the Gmail web version to send and receive emails, but it takes nearly a minute to load the standard Gmail webpage when the internet is smooth, and scrolling through emails is a disaster.</description></item><item><title>Installing macOS Catalina on Unsupported Devices</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macos-catalina-on-unsupport-mac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 10:41:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/macos-catalina-on-unsupport-mac/</guid><description>Some computers may still work perfectly fine, but they may be removed from the upgrade list by official sources due to multiple considerations, such as performance, commercial, or functional considerations. Isn&amp;rsquo;t it a shame?
At this time, dosdude1 has solved this problem with the Catalina Patcher.
This is the official support list:
Screenshot from Apple official website
Below is the Catalina Patcher support list, which is consistent with the OS X El Capitan system requirements:</description></item><item><title>Experience ChromiumOS with CloudReady and Give Your Old Computer a New Life!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/cloudready/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 15:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/cloudready/</guid><description>Have you ever experienced a situation where your old computer is struggling to handle basic tasks like document processing and web browsing? You may not want to use an outdated operating system that is no longer supported by the official provider, including the browser. In this case, you can download the latest version of CloudReady Home Edition to breathe new life into your computer. It comes with the latest browser and many Web Apps that you can use.</description></item><item><title>How to Use an Android Phone as a Network Connection for a Mac</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/horndis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 07:23:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/horndis/</guid><description>Sometimes, for various reasons, you may not want to use Wi-Fi or a personal hotspot when using the internet, or your computer&amp;rsquo;s wireless network card may be blocked by surrounding objects, or even a black Apple computer may not have a compatible wireless network card. In these cases, using an Android phone as a network receiver is a good idea.
macOS version 10.11 (El Captain) or higher is required, and this article demonstrates using macOS 10.</description></item><item><title>Add Real-time Lyrics to Spotify (iOS/iPadOS)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/no-premium-spotify-dynamic-lyrics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/no-premium-spotify-dynamic-lyrics/</guid><description>Last time, I introduced a comparison of free memberships for various streaming platforms. You may have noticed that many platforms have real-time lyrics, but according to my testing, only Spotify Premium users can use them, which is a bit of a shame.
Do you want to listen to free music on Spotify, but find it inconvenient to sing without lyrics? This article can help you solve this problem.
This article is for iOS/iPadOS users, while Android users can refer to another article instead.</description></item><item><title>[2020 Latest] Comparison of Major Streaming Platforms with Free Membership</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/free-streaming-music-compare/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 12:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/free-streaming-music-compare/</guid><description>蘿蔔 has been searching for free and easy-to-use streaming music platforms for the past few years, so she has almost used all the common platforms in Taiwan. Therefore, she will introduce each platform to you one by one.
First of all, 蘿蔔 is Taiwanese, so some of the platforms introduced in this article may not be available in other countries or regions, and some platforms may have been updated and this article may not have been updated in time.</description></item><item><title>Hosting Static Websites with Github - Github Pages</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/github-static-website/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 14:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/github-static-website/</guid><description>First, go to Github and click on the green New button on the left.
Enter a Repository name (customizable)
Choose Public or Private
Click on Create Repository
Now you have created a Repository!
Next, we need to download Github Desktop to easily upload the website source files.
Click on Download for macOS (or Download for Windows for Windows)
After downloading, sign in to your Github account (Sign in to Github.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Custom Email Domain with Mailgun and Gmail</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/mailgun-gmail-custom-domain-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 12:48:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/mailgun-gmail-custom-domain-email/</guid><description>As a child, I was always curious about the domain name of the sender in an email. Later, after getting involved in website development, I registered many domains (currently having about 6 domains), and gradually understood the doubts I had as a child.
Today, I will share with you the method of setting up custom email domain with Mailgun and Gmail!
First, register with Mailgun, which offers 5000 free emails by default.</description></item></channel></rss>