<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>G-Suite on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/g-suite/</link><description>Recent content in G-Suite on SteveYi's Blog</description><image><url>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</url><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 15:32:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/g-suite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Speed up email loading on old devices and slow internet with traditional version of Gmail</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/html-gmail/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 15:32:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/html-gmail/</guid><description>The author has an old PC with 1GB of memory and Windows XP, which is suitable for light document use (Windows XP only requires 128MB of memory to operate). It can handle browsing some websites, but some large websites take a long time to load or cannot be used normally. If it is a general article webpage, it can still be managed. The problem is that the author wants to use the Gmail web version to send and receive emails, but it takes nearly a minute to load the standard Gmail webpage when the internet is smooth, and scrolling through emails is a disaster.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Cloud Identity account</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-cloud-identity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 20:35:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-cloud-identity/</guid><description>First, go to the Cloud Identity registration page and click on the next page button.
Then enter your company name (you can enter any name), number of employees (choose any number) and treat it as a team.
Select your location (once set, it cannot be changed), but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter.
Set up your current email address (some registration emails will be sent here).
Enter the domain you want to set up (cannot be used for other G Suite services).</description></item><item><title>Delete G Suite organization</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/delete-gsuite/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 18:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/delete-gsuite/</guid><description>Previously, I shared with you the way to register a G Suite account. Recently, I wanted to delete the G Suite organization of the Cloud Identity free version.
Since I have never deleted a G Suite organization before, I searched for information and roughly sorted out the deletion method.
Important reminder: Before deletion, please cancel the contractual authorization and delete all GCP projects. After deletion, all organization data will be cleared.</description></item><item><title>Applying for a G Suite account</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/register-gsuite/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/register-gsuite/</guid><description>I believe most of you have used Gmail before. Today, we want to introduce G Suite, an enterprise service launched by Google. However, individual users can also apply for it!
Preparation: Domain (not necessary) Credit card/Debit card
Registration process: First, let&amp;rsquo;s open the G Suite official website (https://gsuite.google.com)
Next, click &amp;ldquo;Start Free Trial&amp;rdquo;
Enter the company name (or any name you want) on the top. Choose the number of employees (I selected 1).</description></item></channel></rss>