<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>BGP on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/bgp/</link><description>Recent content in BGP on SteveYi's Blog</description><image><url>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</url><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 05:35:35 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/bgp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using AS-SET to build filters</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-as-set-to-make-filter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 05:35:35 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-as-set-to-make-filter/</guid><description>Recently, in order to establish BGP Peers with some friends who are new to the field, I also taught them how to use AS-SET for filtering.
What is AS-SET AS-SET is an object that can add ASN and AS-SET.
Usually used to filter routes exchanged through the BGP protocol. (such as BGP Peer Neighbor, Internet Exchange Route Server, etc.)
We usually query all Route Objects in this AS-SET through Whois and recursion.</description></item><item><title>Become a MANRS participant!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/join-manrs-as-participants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:03:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/join-manrs-as-participants/</guid><description>At the end of last year, I submitted an application for MANRS for SteveYi Network Service. At the beginning of this year, we passed the review and officially became a participant in MANRS! Our member introduction can be found here: https://www.manrs.org/isps/participants/entry/1484/
So, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about how we implement MANRS policies.
MANRS has four main policies, which are:
Prevent propagation of incorrect routing information Prevent traffic with incorrect spoofed source IP addresses Promote coordination between network operators Facilitate global operational communication and coordination</description></item><item><title>Building an Internal Network with Friends using BGP</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/make-internal-network-by-bgp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/make-internal-network-by-bgp/</guid><description>Hi! Long time no see!
In early 2020, I obtained my first ASN number - AS209557
I also used IP Addresses defined by RFC 1918, and with some friends, I built a large internal network using BGP and Internet tunnels.
So let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
First, we use Ubuntu 20.04 to establish a tunnel and establish BGP peerings with others.
Usually, I use GRE, SIT, or WireGuard.
Among them, GRE or SIT tunnels are non-encrypted tunnels that can be viewed on the public network.</description></item><item><title>Applying for your own ASN through RIPE</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/get-asn-from-ripe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 08:39:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/get-asn-from-ripe/</guid><description>Today we will talk about how to obtain your own ASN through LIR in RIPE.
First of all, some people may wonder:
Why choose RIPE? Isn&amp;rsquo;t APNIC or ARIN a good choice?
The author has two ASNs, one under RIPE and the other under APNIC. When the author makes changes to some whois information, RIPE allows direct web access to make changes, while APNIC requires sending emails&amp;hellip; which is more troublesome (actually it&amp;rsquo;s about the same).</description></item><item><title>Creating Objects in RIPE DataBase</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-object-in-ripe-database/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 08:37:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/create-object-in-ripe-database/</guid><description>In this article, we will share with you how to register MAINTAINER, PERSON/ROLE, and ORGANIZATION objects in the RIPE DataBase.
These objects are also necessary to register ASN. If you want to apply for ASN, you can refer to this tutorial.
First, we need to register for a RIPE account registration website here.
After completing the registration, we enter the RIPE Database and click &amp;ldquo;Create an Object&amp;rdquo;.
Then we select the first &amp;ldquo;role and maintainer pair&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Building interconnectivity between different network segments through BGP</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/bgp-network-peer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 18:56:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/bgp-network-peer/</guid><description>As a child, I often struggled with managing my home network. For example, my home had three floors and three routers. I wanted to make sure that devices connected to each router could communicate with each other. However, if I turned on DHCP Server on each of the routers, the routers would become independent networks that couldn&amp;rsquo;t communicate with each other.
Later, I discovered that by using a bridge to turn one router into a DHCP server and the others into AP or switch, I could achieve the same network and interconnectivity.</description></item><item><title>FRRouting Installation Tutorial</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/frrouting-install/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 13:07:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/frrouting-install/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I last shared anything! Recently, I have been learning about BGP knowledge and testing. Previously, I used Bird1 to broadcast BGP, but when I tried to peer with my friend, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t establish a connection (it was strange, but I could connect with IX). So I uninstalled Bird1 and installed FRRouting instead.
FRRouting is a routing suite that comes from Quagga Fork, and its functionality is also very powerful (its commands are similar to Cisco or Quagga).</description></item><item><title>Using WireGuard on Linux</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/how-to-use-wireguard/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 11:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/how-to-use-wireguard/</guid><description>WireGuard is a point-to-point encryption network. I have been using it to manage/connect all my cloud servers.
Today, let&amp;rsquo;s share how to use WireGuard!
Install WireGuard Basically, the WireGuard Install Page provides complete installation methods and commands for various versions, so you can refer to it directly.
Create WireGuard Profile First, go to the WireGuard installation folder. If it does not exist, please create it.
cd /etc/wireguard Use the command to generate a public and private key, and use &amp;ldquo;cat&amp;rdquo; to view the contents of the public and private keys.</description></item><item><title>Announce IPv6 on Vultr with BIRD</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-bird6-broadcast-ipv6-vultr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 02:21:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-bird6-broadcast-ipv6-vultr/</guid><description>It is recommended to refer to the article Building an Internal Network with Friends via BGP on January 24, 2021.
This time, let&amp;rsquo;s share how to broadcast IP on Vultr!
Setting the AS number and IP prefix First, we need to activate the BGP function! Click here to go to the Vultr BGP page After entering this page, click Get Started.
Select I have my own IP space and I have own my ASN (if there is no ASN, you do not need to select it)</description></item></channel></rss>