<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>object storage on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/object-storage/</link><description>Recent content in object storage on SteveYi's Blog</description><image><url>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</url><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/images/banner.webp</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 03:08:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/object-storage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Backblaze B2 now supports S3 API!</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2-compatible-s3-api/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 03:08:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2-compatible-s3-api/</guid><description>A few days ago, when I opened Backblaze, I saw a big line of text:
That&amp;rsquo;s right! Backblaze B2 now supports the S3 API!
The S3 API is currently the most popular protocol in the market, and many hardware and software are compatible.
Backblaze B2 is a great cloud storage option with a low cost advantage.
How to use the S3 API If the storage bucket was created before May 4, 2020, you will need to create a new one and move your files into it (we recommend using Rclone, which will automatically support B2 Copy File).</description></item><item><title>Backblaze B2: Affordable Cloud Data Storage Service</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backblaze-b2/</guid><description>When I was learning how to build a website, I considered a problem!
If my traffic suddenly increased and I had more articles, would my image storage and bandwidth also increase?
So I searched for some object storage services online and found a cheap object storage provider - Backblaze.
What is Object Storage? Object storage is a type of data storage where each data unit is stored as a discrete unit called an object.</description></item></channel></rss>