<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Android on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/android/</link><description>Recent content in Android on SteveYi's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 07:23:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/android/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Use an Android Phone as a Network Connection for a Mac</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/horndis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 07:23:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/horndis/</guid><description>Sometimes, for various reasons, you may not want to use Wi-Fi or a personal hotspot when using the internet, or your computer&amp;rsquo;s wireless network card may be blocked by surrounding objects, or even a black Apple computer may not have a compatible wireless network card. In these cases, using an Android phone as a network receiver is a good idea.
macOS version 10.11 (El Captain) or higher is required, and this article demonstrates using macOS 10.</description></item><item><title>Method to add real-time lyrics to Spotify or other music software (Android)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/dynamic-lyrics-android/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 10:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/dynamic-lyrics-android/</guid><description>Last time, we introduced the comparison of free memberships among various streaming platforms. As you can see, many platforms have real-time lyrics. However, according to our testing, only Spotify Premium users can use them, and some platforms do not offer lyric services, which is a bit of a shame.
Do you find it inconvenient to listen to free music on Spotify or other platforms without lyrics? If so, follow this article to solve this problem.</description></item><item><title>[2020 Latest] Comparison of Major Streaming Platforms with Free Membership</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/free-streaming-music-compare/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 12:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/free-streaming-music-compare/</guid><description>蘿蔔 has been searching for free and easy-to-use streaming music platforms for the past few years, so she has almost used all the common platforms in Taiwan. Therefore, she will introduce each platform to you one by one.
First of all, 蘿蔔 is Taiwanese, so some of the platforms introduced in this article may not be available in other countries or regions, and some platforms may have been updated and this article may not have been updated in time.</description></item><item><title>Automatically categorize LINE chat messages into friends, groups, and official accounts</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/line-xun-xi-fen-lei/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 12:25:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/line-xun-xi-fen-lei/</guid><description>It will be much more convenient to find messages after LINE categorizes them&amp;hellip;
This feature is currently only available on Android, but it should be added to iOS in the near future.
Please make sure that your LINE version is the latest version on Google Play.
First, open LINE and go to the main page.
Next, click on the gear icon in the upper right corner, find LINE Lab, and check the box.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy background playback on Android devices without subscribing to Youtube Music Premium (works for Youtube too!)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-playing-android/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 15:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-playing-android/</guid><description>This guide is primarily demonstrated on an Android phone, although the same method can be applied to Android tablets.
For iOS/iPadOS users, a similar method can be used as described in this post.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get started First, open Youtube Music homepage on Chrome browser (most devices with built-in Google Play services should have it, if not, you can download it here) and do not play any music yet. Click the three dots on the top right corner and check &amp;ldquo;Desktop site&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Use IFTTT to Turn off Wi-Fi When Leaving Home</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ifttt-zhi-dong-guan-wifi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 04:43:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/ifttt-zhi-dong-guan-wifi/</guid><description>As I often forget to turn off Wi-Fi when leaving home, I found this method to solve the problem.
First, we need to prepare according to different device types.
For Xiaomi, Redmi, Black Shark, and POCO phone users First, lock and allow IFTTT to self-start and set the power-saving policy to unrestricted from the recent apps. Skip this section if not applicable.
Press and hold the IFTTT preview icon to bring up the menu below.</description></item><item><title>Fixing the issue of Telegram automatically switching back to the default theme when dark mode is enabled on Android</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/telegram-dark-mode-theme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 08:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/telegram-dark-mode-theme/</guid><description>If you have changed the theme on Telegram, you may have noticed that it always switches back to the default dark blue theme when dark mode is enabled on Android.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a solution to this problem:
First, open the side menu and select &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo;.
Next, select &amp;ldquo;Chat Settings&amp;rdquo;.
Finally, find &amp;ldquo;Auto-Night Mode&amp;rdquo; and turn it off.</description></item><item><title>Tips for Improving Mobile Phone Audio Quality</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/yin-zhi-ti-sheng/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 03:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/yin-zhi-ti-sheng/</guid><description>Note: This article also applies to Apple Lightning devices and most USB-C devices, such as Windows computers.
While you may think that the audio quality of your headphones that cost just over $20 is bad, have you overlooked an important detail? Although using headphones from the same brand as your phone may result in better optimization, it cannot be denied that the built-in DAC (an important component that converts digital audio into analog signals and provides them to headphones) of your phone may not be as good as an external DAC.</description></item><item><title>Using TeamViewer to Remotely Control Android Phones</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/teamviewer-android/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:09:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/teamviewer-android/</guid><description>Do you often forget to bring your Android phone with you when you need it? TeamViewer can help with that! But you need to remove it from the system&amp;rsquo;s automatic background kill list.
The remote control function is compatible with Android 5~Android 8 (the first time you use it, you may be asked for permission, and you can choose to allow permanently). For Android 9 and above, it is suitable for remote viewing (every time you use it on Android 9 and above, you need to allow it once on your phone, which is more suitable as a tool for wireless display to a computer).</description></item><item><title>Easily Install APK Files to Your Phone with Scrcpy</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/scrcpy-android-apk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 08:52:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/scrcpy-android-apk/</guid><description>First, we need to install Scrcpy and open it.
Installation instructions here
If you are using a Xiaomi phone (if not, skip this part),
go to &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;Additional settings&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;Developer options&amp;rdquo; and allow USB installation.
This action requires a SIM card to be inserted (required by MIUI).
Please have the Finder or File Manager window for the prepared APK file open on the side, and drag the file into the Scrcpy window.</description></item><item><title>Using Scrcpy to Control Your Android Phone from Your Computer</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/scrcpy-android/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 15:41:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/scrcpy-android/</guid><description>Introduction: Due to a sudden breakdown of the screen of my phone, the liquid crystal display (LCD) would display but with no backlight, making it difficult to view the screen. However, I still needed to use the phone to transfer important data and test Android programs. Therefore, I had to figure out a way to operate it! (As I currently use an iPhone)
(Screen can only be vaguely seen under intense light)</description></item></channel></rss>