<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>iOS on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/ios/</link><description>Recent content in iOS on SteveYi's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:35:46 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/ios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using checkm8 Activation Lock Free Version to Bypass iOS Activation Lock</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/checkm8-bypass/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:35:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/checkm8-bypass/</guid><description>This article is also published on &amp;ldquo;蘿蔔&amp;rsquo;s Blog&amp;rdquo;
[Note] Please do not use for commercial or illegal purposes.
This software was not developed by the author. The author is not responsible for any controversies arising from its use. To bypass activation lock, you need a Mac computer.
The author tested the software on their own device with their own account (iPhone 7 Plus, iOS 14.3). Sometimes, due to certain reasons, when an iPhone is reset or updated without turning off &amp;ldquo;Find My&amp;rdquo;, you will be asked for the Apple ID password to disable activation lock when resetting it.</description></item><item><title>Backing up Installed Plugins with Redeb</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-redeb-to-backup-jb-tweaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 04:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/use-redeb-to-backup-jb-tweaks/</guid><description>A long time ago, the author encountered a situation where a plugin disappeared from another source, preventing them from installing the desired plugin. However, because the plugin was installed on another device, they were able to back up the deb file and install it on the desired device. This article is for those who want to back up their plugins!
Redeb and the backed up deb files (using Zebra as an example)</description></item><item><title>Super useful built-in Spotlight search tips on iOS and macOS</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/apple-spotlight/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 09:02:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/apple-spotlight/</guid><description>Many people have bought iPhones, iPads, iPod touches, or Macs, but they don&amp;rsquo;t know that the built-in Spotlight has many useful features. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look!
How to use Spotlight (the method may be different in earlier versions): On iOS/iPadOS, swipe down on the home screen; on macOS, click on the magnifying glass in the menu bar (top right corner), or press &amp;ldquo;command&amp;rdquo; + &amp;ldquo;space bar&amp;rdquo;.
Note: The search function of Spotlight and Siri has improved with each version, so some older versions may not have certain features.</description></item><item><title>Add Real-time Lyrics to Spotify (iOS/iPadOS)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/no-premium-spotify-dynamic-lyrics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/no-premium-spotify-dynamic-lyrics/</guid><description>Last time, I introduced a comparison of free memberships for various streaming platforms. You may have noticed that many platforms have real-time lyrics, but according to my testing, only Spotify Premium users can use them, which is a bit of a shame.
Do you want to listen to free music on Spotify, but find it inconvenient to sing without lyrics? This article can help you solve this problem.
This article is for iOS/iPadOS users, while Android users can refer to another article instead.</description></item><item><title>[2020 Latest] Comparison of Major Streaming Platforms with Free Membership</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/free-streaming-music-compare/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 12:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/free-streaming-music-compare/</guid><description>蘿蔔 has been searching for free and easy-to-use streaming music platforms for the past few years, so she has almost used all the common platforms in Taiwan. Therefore, she will introduce each platform to you one by one.
First of all, 蘿蔔 is Taiwanese, so some of the platforms introduced in this article may not be available in other countries or regions, and some platforms may have been updated and this article may not have been updated in time.</description></item><item><title>No subscription required for Youtube Music Premium to enable background playback on iOS/iPadOS (also works for Youtube!)</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-ios/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 14:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/youtube-background-ios/</guid><description>Here we mainly use iPad as an example, but the same method can be applied to iPhone as well. Android devices can also use a similar method, and a tutorial for Android will be posted in the future, so stay tuned for more articles from &amp;ldquo;I am Little Yi&amp;rdquo;!
Update: Android tutorial is available here
Recently, the author has been looking for a good free streaming music service, and found that the Youtube Music App on the computer (actually embedded in the webpage) is quite user-friendly.</description></item><item><title>Tips for Improving Mobile Phone Audio Quality</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/yin-zhi-ti-sheng/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 03:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/yin-zhi-ti-sheng/</guid><description>Note: This article also applies to Apple Lightning devices and most USB-C devices, such as Windows computers.
While you may think that the audio quality of your headphones that cost just over $20 is bad, have you overlooked an important detail? Although using headphones from the same brand as your phone may result in better optimization, it cannot be denied that the built-in DAC (an important component that converts digital audio into analog signals and provides them to headphones) of your phone may not be as good as an external DAC.</description></item><item><title>Downgrade 32-bit iOS Devices to 8.4.1 without Computer and SHSH</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backtoios841/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 13:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/backtoios841/</guid><description>Sometimes there may be problems with Apple, causing various problems. If there are any errors, please try again another day.
Apple&amp;rsquo;s vulnerabilities are not very stable. I tried three times in one day and couldn&amp;rsquo;t use them. I succeeded once another day. This is a bit of luck.
If the iOS device is slow, downgrading will be smoother
(A5 devices are very noticeable, while A6 and A6X devices are not much different but still a bit faster)</description></item></channel></rss>