<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>VPS on SteveYi's Blog</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/vps/</link><description>Recent content in VPS on SteveYi's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>tw</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 18:31:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steveyi.net/en/tags/vps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building an Internal Network with WireGuard</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-wireguard-to-make-intranet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/using-wireguard-to-make-intranet/</guid><description>Hi everyone, today I&amp;rsquo;m going to share how to use WireGuard to build an internal network.
Previously, I shared how to install WireGuard on Linux systems. This time, we will use WireGuard to build an internal network.
Why Build an Internal Network? Why does the author call this an &amp;ldquo;internal network&amp;rdquo;? Because the author may be in different places and wants to use this opportunity to add them all to the same LAN.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Tunnel Broker Service (v4 to v6) on Ubuntu System</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/tunnel-broker-bgp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 16:56:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/tunnel-broker-bgp/</guid><description>Introduction I recently obtained an Autonomous System Number (AS Number), along with one /44 and two /48 IPv6 addresses. Coincidentally, I remembered using HE.Net&amp;rsquo;s tunnel broker service before, so I decided to set up a sit tunnel broker service. This article does not explain how to obtain IPv6 addresses, please consult your hosting provider.
This article will use the open source tool - IPv6-in-IPv4 Tunnel.
Configuration tool First, download the tool:</description></item><item><title>Windows 10 DD Image specifically for GCP</title><link>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/gcp-windows-dd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 15:07:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.steveyi.net/en/posts/gcp-windows-dd/</guid><description>Recently, in order to use VPS on GCP, I created a Windows DD image during a period of time. The images are:
Traditional Chinese version of Windows 10 Workstation Professional Edition English version of Windows 10 Workstation Professional Edition (not uploaded yet) The image has the following features:
Integrated with Virtio driver and Google Virtio Ethernet Adapter network card driver, suitable for GCP VPS servers Unattended installation without VNC interaction. Once DD is completed, you can remotely log in to the desktop Made based on VOL version, so the system can be activated by KMS method Turn on Windows Remote Desktop Traditional Chinese version Download link: http://static-a1.</description></item></channel></rss>